<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Devops on The Fuzzy Spork</title>
    <link>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/tags/devops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Devops on The Fuzzy Spork</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 12:29:54 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/tags/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps and Management</title>
      <link>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2018/03/25/devops-and-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 12:29:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2018/03/25/devops-and-management/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: What do you do if your management doesn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;get&amp;rdquo; DevOps and Continuous Integration/Continuous Deployment?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searching for SSL Certificates based on SAN entries</title>
      <link>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2017/12/23/searching-for-ssl-certificates-based-on-san-entries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 08:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2017/12/23/searching-for-ssl-certificates-based-on-san-entries/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing with &lt;a href=&#34;https://letsencrypt.org/&#34;&gt;Lets Encrypt&lt;/a&gt; as a means to encrypt public(ish) web-based services I run on my local server. It&amp;rsquo;s actually remarkable what this non-profit group has accomplished when it comes to SSL - they offer free, automated SSL certificates to anybody who wants them. They even support SAN certificates (those that cover multiple, explicitly-named DNS entries), and starting in January they will offer wildcard certificates. I will tell anybody who is willing to listen, and who is looking to avoid paying paying $50+ for an SSL certificate, about them and encourage everyone to look into their service. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Octopus Deploy to deploy multiple projects at once</title>
      <link>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2017/12/14/using-octopus-deploy-to-deploy-multiple-projects-at-once/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2017/12/14/using-octopus-deploy-to-deploy-multiple-projects-at-once/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We use Octopus Deploy at my workplace to handle all of our releases. The tool is one of the best I&amp;rsquo;ve had the pleasure of dealing with, and the more I interact with it, the more I realize just how powerful, yet flexible, it is. I will gladly recommend it to anyone who is looking for a way of releasing any kind of software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, there is always room for improvement. In this case, not necessarily improvement with the software package, but how we use it. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On deployments and distribution</title>
      <link>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2016/10/11/on-deployments-and-distribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2016/10/11/on-deployments-and-distribution/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ever since I started programming, I&amp;rsquo;ve been fascinated with what you can do with a codebase - not just the act of programming, but building and deploying it as well. For a programming company, the less time programmers have to work on building or deploying their code, the more productive they can be. The automation of these things can have a huge benefit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>