<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Fuzzy Spork</title>
    <link>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Fuzzy Spork</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 08:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Searching for SSL Certificates based on SAN entries</title>
      <link>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2017/12/23/searching-for-ssl-certificates-based-on-san-entries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 08:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2017/12/23/searching-for-ssl-certificates-based-on-san-entries/</guid>
      <description>Lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing with Lets Encrypt as a means to encrypt public(ish) web-based services I run on my local server. It&amp;rsquo;s actually remarkable what this non-profit group has accomplished when it comes to SSL - they offer free, automated SSL certificates to anybody who wants them. They even support SAN certificates (those that cover multiple, explicitly-named DNS entries), and starting in January they will offer wildcard certificates. I will tell anybody who is willing to listen, and who is looking to avoid paying paying $50+ for an SSL certificate, about them and encourage everyone to look into their service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Octopus Deploy to deploy multiple projects at once</title>
      <link>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2017/12/14/using-octopus-deploy-to-deploy-multiple-projects-at-once/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2017/12/14/using-octopus-deploy-to-deploy-multiple-projects-at-once/</guid>
      <description>We use Octopus Deploy at my workplace to handle all of our releases. The tool is one of the best I&amp;rsquo;ve had the pleasure of dealing with, and the more I interact with it, the more I realize just how powerful, yet flexible, it is. I will gladly recommend it to anyone who is looking for a way of releasing any kind of software.
However, there is always room for improvement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing Expectations</title>
      <link>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2017/08/02/managing-expectations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 13:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2017/08/02/managing-expectations/</guid>
      <description>This morning I realized that, as programmers, we frequently make assumptions about the software we write which seem to be reasonable, but aren&amp;rsquo;t completely thought out.I have an older (second generation) iPad that I mostly use for playing games and managing a media server I have set up in my house. Occasionally I will use it as a note-taking device, but honestly it can&amp;rsquo;t do much more, and I don&amp;rsquo;t need it to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Non-standard Developer</title>
      <link>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2017/04/05/the-non-standard-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2017/04/05/the-non-standard-developer/</guid>
      <description>I recently read this really awesome article written by a developer who had no formal education or background and his journey to becoming a front-end developer. Having gone through a somewhat similar transformation, I was inspired to also write about my own transition into programming without a traditional programming background. Who are you anyway? A fair question, and one I&amp;rsquo;m going to avoid almost entirely. Instead, I&amp;rsquo;m going to say that my formal education is in business, specifically accounting, and that my transition into pure development wasn&amp;rsquo;t radical, but a career evolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On deployments and distribution</title>
      <link>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2016/10/11/on-deployments-and-distribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2016/10/11/on-deployments-and-distribution/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I started programming, I&amp;rsquo;ve been fascinated with what you can do with a codebase - not just the act of programming, but building and deploying it as well. For a programming company, the less time programmers have to work on building or deploying their code, the more productive they can be. The automation of these things can have a huge benefit.I&amp;rsquo;m sure many who may be reading this already have something in place to automatically build code, either on check-in, at a specific time, or both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fuzzy Spork</title>
      <link>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2016/10/05/the-fuzzy-spork/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kingofzeal.github.io/fuzzy-spork/2016/10/05/the-fuzzy-spork/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A fascinating picture, isn&amp;rsquo;t it? A fuzzy spork. It conjures images that raise far more questions than they answer. What does it mean? What could make a spork fuzzy? Is it safe? Is it supposed to be like that? Is it really a fuzzy spork or is it a sporked fuzzy? Where are the adults?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>